Guide to the Agenda Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1925-1984; Series I; 15.5; (31 boxes)
  - Levi, Peter
    - [Review] "F. T. Prince. Drypoints of the Hasidim "
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 17, Folder 1176)
      - Galley with author's corrections, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1177)
    - "Five Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 1178)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1179)
    - "For Charles Haldeman"
      - Printed version, corrected, undated (Box 17, Folder 1180)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 17, Folder 1181)
    - "For Denis Bethen," typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 1182)
    - "Four Chinese Poets," from literal translations by John Cayley, holograph, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1183)
    - [Review] "Gary Synder," holograph, corrected, undated (Box 17, Folder 1184)
    - "History and Reality in David Jones"
      - Holograph
        See: Oversize, Box 57, folder 2792
      - Typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 1185)
    - [Review] Mercian Hymns, by Geoffrey Hill, typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 1186)
    - "Notes on Myth"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 17, Folder 1187)
      - Galleys, with author's corrections, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1188)
    - "Officers and Gentlemen"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 1189)
      - Galley with author's corrections, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1190)
        With: ALS to William Cookson from Peter Levi, 1975 Feb 28
    - [Review] "Penelope Palmer. The Lamp, A Selection of Poems ," holograph, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1191)
    - [Review] "Peter Russell's All for the Wolves "
      - Holograph, corrected, undated (Box 17, Folder 1192)
      - Galley with author's corrections, undated (Box 17, Folder 1193)
    - [Review] "The Poetry of Cesar Vallejo," typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 1194)
    - "Pound and the Classics," holograph, undated (Box 17, Folder 1195)
    - "Seven Poems," typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 1196)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 1197)
    - [Review] Virgil's Aeneid, by Gavin Douglas, holograph, undated (Box 17, Folder 1198)
    - Untitled article, galley, undated (Box 17, Folder 1199)
    - Untitled article, holograph, 1977 Oct 10 (Box 17, Folder 1200)
    - Untitled article, holograph, corrected, with a note from Peter Levi to William Cookson, undated (Box 17, Folder 1201)
  - Li, Po
    - "Drinking Alone in Moonshine," translated by Arthur Cooper, autograph ms., undated (Box 17, Folder 1202)
  - Lieberman, Laurence
    - "The Osprey Suicides," printed version, photocopy, 1972 Nov 25 (Box 17, Folder 1203)
  - Linden, Eddie
    - "The Miner," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 17, Folder 1204)
  - Liu, Nienling
    - "Concerned Aesthetes And Aesthetic Concerns," typescript and electrostat copy, 1982 Jul (Box 17, Folder 1205)
  - Liu, Tao-t'ao (Tao Tao Liu)
    - "Modern Chinese Poetry," typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 1206)
  - Logan, John
    - "David and Isabel," typescript, mimeograph, corrected, undated (Box 17, Folder 1207)
    - "Elegy for the Rev. Mr. James B. Hodgson," typescript, mimeograph, 1966 Mar 16 (Box 17, Folder 1208)
    - "On The Death of Keats," typescript, annotated, undated (Box 17, Folder 1209)
    - "White Pass Ski Patrol," typescript, 1966 Feb 19 (Box 17, Folder 1210)
  - Logue, Christopher
    - "Examinations Every Night"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1211)
      - Galley, undated (Box 18, Folder 1212)
    - "From GBH"
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 18, Folder 1213)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1214)
  - London, Carole
    - "Time"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1215)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1216)
  - Lorca, Federico García
    - "Ballad of the Spanish Civil Guards," translated by Michael Reck, typescript, original with Spanish version, undated (Box 18, Folder 1217)
    - "Saint Eulalia's Martyrdom," translated by Michael Reck, typescript, with Spanish version, undated (Box 18, Folder 1218)
  - Lovelock, Yann
    - "Ode: And suddenly the Moon erupts," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1219)
    - "Seriously," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1220)
    - "Sestina," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1221)
    - "Something Nasty in the Supermarket," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1222)
    - "Two Kinds of Pain in a Ward," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1223)
  - Lowbury, Edward
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1224)
  - Lowell, Robert
    - "Five Poems" (from Day by Day )
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1225)
      - Galley with author's corrections, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1226)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1227)
    - "Letter to the Editor," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1228)
    - "The Mills of the Kavanaughs," printed version, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 1229)
  - Lowery, Phillip
    - "A Letter," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1230)
  - Lu, Li (Lu Li)
    - "The Shell," unidentified translator, printed version, undated (Box 18, Folder 1231)
  - Lu, Lu (Lu Lu)
    - "Two Poems," unidentified translator, printed version, undated (Box 18, Folder 1232)
  - Lu, Y'uan (Lü Yuan)
    - "When I Was Young," unidentified, translator, printed version, undated (Box 18, Folder 1233)
  - Lucretius Carus, Titus
    - [ De Reum Natura ,] "Book VI," translated by C. H. Sisson, uncorrected proof, photocopy with a note to William Cookson from Michael [Hamburger], 1975 (Box 18, Folder 1234)
  - Lungu, Vera
    - "Anniversary," translated by Vera Lungu and Anne Beresford, typescript, corrected, 3 drafts, undated (Box 18, Folder 1235)
  - Lyon, Martin
    - "Inscription for a Pocket Latin Dictionary," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1236)
  - Ma, Chih-yüan (Ma, Zhiyuan)
    - "Returning Sails across the Bay," translated by John Cayley, poem, typescript, original, undated (Box 18, Folder 1237)
  - Maass, Donald
    - "Haiku"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1238)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 18, Folder 1239)
  - Maas, [?]
    - "Ocean Crossing," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1240)
    - "Together," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1241)
  - MacBeth, George
    - "Response to Rhythm Questionnaire," galley, undated (Box 18, Folder 1242)
  - McCarthy, Patricia
    - "Four Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1243)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1244)
    - "Gemini," galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 18, Folder 1244a)
    - "Love Child"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1245)
      - Galley, with author's corrections [2 c.], undated (Box 18, Folder 1246)
    - "Origins," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1247)
    - "Persistences," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1248)
    - "Three Poems," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1249)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1250)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1251)
  - McCarthy, Shaun
    - [Review] "Edward Lowbury, Goldrush ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1252)
    - [Review] "Peter Levi: Private Ground ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1253)
    - [Review] "The Poetry of C. H. Sisson"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1254)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1255)
  - McCormick, Michael
    - "Hands," typescript, corrected, 1974 Jun 6 (Box 18, Folder 1256)
    - "Three Poems," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1257)
  - MacDiarmid, Hugh
    - "The Auld Houff," typescript, with holograph notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 1258)
    - "The Borders," galley, with author's corrections, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 1259)
    - "Bracken Hills in Autumn," holograph, undated (Box 18, Folder 1260)
    - "Credo for a Celtic Poet," holograph, undated (Box 18, Folder 1261)
    - "The Day Before the Twelfth," typescript, with holograph notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 1262)
    - "The Esemplastic Power," galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 18, Folder 1263)
    - "Gavin Douglas and the Aeneid"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1264)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1265)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 18, Folder 1266)
        - With: ALS to William Cookson from Christopher Grieve [Hugh MacDiarmid], 1976 Oct 7
    - [Review] "John Montagu's Ulster"
      - Holograph, undated (Box 18, Folder 1267)
      - Typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1268)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 18, Folder 1269)
    - [Review] "The Master-Voyageur of our Age"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1270)
      - Typescript, corrected, p.5-8, undated (Box 18, Folder 1271)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 18, Folder 1272)
    - "The Nature of a Bird's World," holograph, with notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 1273)
    - [Review] "A Neglected Poet and Faithful Servant of the Muses," holograph, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 1274)
    - "Note on Paysages Legendaires," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1275)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1276)
      - Galley, corrected, 1975. (Box 18, Folder 1277)
        With: ANS to William Cookson from Christopher Grieve, 1975 Feb 24
    - "When the Birds Come Back to Rhiannon," holograph, undated (Box 18, Folder 1278)
    - [Review] "William Dunbar, Scotland's Greatest Hero," holograph, undated (Box 18, Folder 1279)
      - With: ALS to William Cookson from Christopher Grieve, [Hugh MacDiarmid], 1966 Sep 9
  - Mackenney, Julian
    - "Spleen," typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1280)
  - Mackie, A. D.
    - "Francis MacVillon in Rose Street," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1281)
  - McIntire, Janet
    - "Five Poems," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1282)
  - MacVean, Jean
    - "Another Look at Edith Sitwell"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1283)
      - Galleys, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1284)
    - "Cotswolds - September," poem, typescript, original, undated (Box 18, Folder 1285)
    - "Four Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1286)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1287)
    - [Review] "Kathleen Raine," Collected Poems 1935/1980, by Kathleen Raine, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1288)
    - [Review] "John Montague," Selected Poems, by John Montague, typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 1289)
    - "Near at Hand," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1290)
    - [Review] Temenos, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1291)
    - [Review] Temenos Number Two, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1292)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1293)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1294)
        - With: TLS to William Cookson from Jean MacVean, 1980 Sep 2
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 18, Folder 1295)
  - Makin, Peter
    - "Bunting and Sound"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1296)
      - Typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1297)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 19, Folder 1298)
    - "Kennedy, Fenollosa, Pound, and the Chinese Character"
      - Typescript [2c., one incomplete], undated (Box 19, Folder 1299)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 19, Folder 1300)
      - Galley, undated (Box 19, Folder 1301)
  - Mallarmé, Stéphane
    - "L'Après-Midi D'Un Faune," translated by Stephen Ratcliffe, printed version, photocopy, undated (Box 19, Folder 1302)
  - Mandelstam, Nadezhda
    - Untitled article, typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1303)
  - Mandelstam, Osip
    - [Eight Poems, 1908-30] translated by Peter Russell, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1304)
    - "A Selection from a New Translation by James Green"
      - "Dead-Man's Fall," 1908-37, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1305)
      - "Lapse," "Notre Dame" and two untitled poems, 1911-37, typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1306)
      - [Twenty Poems, 1909-37] typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1307)
  - Mann, Sylvia
    - "No Return," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1308)
  - Marot, Clément
    - "On the Fair Breast," translated by Keith Bosley, typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1309)
  - [Marsworth?]
    - "In Camera," typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1310)
  - Martial
    - "His Wife," poem, translated by Peter Whigham, typescript, original, corrected, signed, undated (Box 19, Folder 1311)
    - "The New Bride," translated by Peter Whigham, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1312)
    - "Versions from Martial," translated by W.S. Milne, poems, typescript, original, signed, undated (Box 19, Folder 1313)
  - Massey, Alan
    - "Basil Bunting Re-Read: A Salute"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1314)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1315)
    - "Flesh and Blood in Poetry"
      - Typescript, 1973 Feb (Box 19, Folder 1316)
      - Galley, with "Three Poems," galley, with typescript author's corrections, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1317)
        With an ANS to William Cookson from Alan Massey, 1975 Feb 23
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1318)
    - "The Horse Flies," galley, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1319)
    - "The Last Quartet," typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1320)
    - "Leechcraft"
      - Typescript, corrected, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 1321)
      - Galley, with typescript corrections, undated (Box 19, Folder 1322)
      - Galley, corrected, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 1323)
    - "The Light-Gathering"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1324)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1325)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1326)
    - "Nets for Mercury"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1327)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 19, Folder 1328)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1329)
    - "Pergola, Fugue, Revolution," typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1330)
    - [Review] "A Poet's Prose"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1331)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 19, Folder 1332)
    - [Review] "Possession and the Individual Possum," typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1333)
    - "A Summer Anthem," typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1334)
    - "Three Poems," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 19, Folder 1335)
    - "Two Horse-Flies," typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1336)
  - Mathews, F. X.
    - "The Concrete Judasbird. The Frog in the Bottom of the Well," typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 1337)
  - Meares, Peter
    - [Review] "Ah Poet, Lucky Poet, A Review of the Book: Station Island ," by Seamus Heaney"
      - Typescript, corrected, 1984 Nov (Box 20, Folder 1338)
      - Typescript, corrected, 1984 Nov (Box 20, Folder 1339)
      - Empty folder (Box 20, Folder 1340)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, [1984] (Box 20, Folder 1341)
  - Medlin, J. F.
    - "Homage to W.H. Auden. 21st Feb 1981," typescript (Box 20, Folder 1342)
    - "A New York Skyline," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1343)
  - Megally, Sahfik
    See: Heath-Stubbs, John
  - Melinescu, Gabriela
    - "Ballad," translated by Vera Lungu, holograph, and typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1344)
  - Merchant, Moelwyn
    - "The Coke Cantos"
      - Typescript, corrected, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1345)
      - Galley, corrected [2 c.], undated (Box 20, Folder 1346)
  - Meschonnic, Henri
    - "Three Poems," translated by F. Giles, holograph and typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1347)
  - Meyer, Bruce
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1348)
      - Galley, undated (Box 20, Folder 1349)
  - Middleton, Christopher
    - "Bishop, Rabbit, and Ducks," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1350)
    - "Invisible Forces," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1351)
    - "Merindol Interior 1970," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1352)
    - "The Monk of Montaudon," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1353)
    - "Old Woman at the County Dump," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1354)
      With: TLS to William Cookson from Christopher Middleton, 1973 May 11
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1355)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1356)
  - Middleton, David
    - "Forgotten Master, Masterpiece: T. Sturge Moore's Daimonassa and the Myth of Ge and Nemesis"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1357)
      - Galley, undated (Box 20, Folder 1358)
    - [Four Chinese Poems], typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1359)
    - With: TLS from David Middleton to William Cookson, 1982 Jul 9
    - [Review] "Reconsiderations Reconsidered," In the Classic Mode, by Donald E. Stanford, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1360)
  - Miller, Christopher
    - "The Egotistical Banal, or Against Larkitudinising"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1361)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 20, Folder 1362)
  - Miller, David
    - "The Caryatids," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1363)
    - "Down by the Riverside," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1364)
    - [Review] "Guy Davenport. The Geography of the Imagination: Forty Essays," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1365)
    - [Review] "Michael Hamburger: Some Remarks on His Poetry"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1366)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 20, Folder 1367)
    - [Review] Prospice 8 (Special Raymond Queneau Issue), edited by Michael Edwards
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1368)
      - Galley, undated (Box 20, Folder 1369)
    - [Review] "Roy Fisher's Matrix "
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1370)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 20, Folder 1371)
    - "Slides"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1372)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 20, Folder 1373)
        With: TLS to William Cookson from David Miller, 1980 Sep 1
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1374)
    - "A Sort of Beguine," typescript, 1978-80 (Box 20, Folder 1375)
    - "Through Fire," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1376)
    - "(Untitled.)" typescript, for Julius Bissier, undated (Box 20, Folder 1377)
  - Milne, Ewart
    - "The Iron Rape," typescript, final draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 1378)
    - [Review] Sheltering Places by Gerald Dawe
      - Typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1379)
      - Galley with author's corrections, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1380)
        With: TLS to William Cookson from Evart Milne, 1979 Jul 20
    - [Review] "The Travail of Irish Poetry"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1381)
      - Galley with author's corrections, undated (Box 20, Folder 1382)
  - Milne, William S.
    - "The Country's Music," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1383)
    - "'Decreation' in Geoffrey Hill's Lachrimae"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1384)
      - Galley with author's corrections, undated (Box 20, Folder 1385)
        With: [Review] "Narrative and Epiphany," by William Bedford, galley, corrected, undated, and [Review] "Heathstubbs at Sixty," by Humphrey Clucas, galley, corrected, undated
      - Galley, undated (Box 20, Folder 1386)
    - [Four Poems], typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1387)
    - "Fremmit," galley with author's corrections, undated (Box 20, Folder 1387a)
    - [Review] "The Genesis of Hugh MacDiarmid"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1388)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1389)
    - [Review] "'Images of Earth and Grace': Geoffrey Hill's The Mystery of the Charity of Charles Péguy "
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1390)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1391)
    - "'The Pitch of Attention': Geoffrey Hill's Tenebrae "
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1392)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 20, Folder 1393)
      - Galley, undated (Box 20, Folder 1394)
    - "A Select Piece," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 20, Folder 1395)
    - "Six Poems," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1396)
    - "Three Poems," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1397)
    - [Three Poems], typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1398)
  - Mitchinson, Naomi
    - [Review] "Wyndham Lewis," typescript, undated (Box 20, Folder 1399)
  - Mole, John
    - "My Pets," typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1400)
  - Montague, John
    - [Response to Rhythm Questionnaire], galleys, with author's corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 1401)
    - "Sea Changes, A sequence of poems for engraving by William Hayter," typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1402)
  - Montale, Eugenio
    - [Review] "Thomas Hardy: Poems edited by G. Singh," and translated by Doreen Davie, typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1403)
    - "Twelve Poems," translated by Keith Bosley, typescript, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 1404)
    - "Twenty Six Poems," translated by Keith Bosley, G. Singh and Bernard Wall, typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1405)
    - "Vecchia Panchina," [in Italian], holograph, undated (Box 21, Folder 1406)
    - Xenia and Motets [Agenda Editions]
      - Typescript, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1407)
      - Galley, undated (Box 21, Folder 1408)
      - Proofs, undated (Box 21, Folder 1409)
      - Proofs, undated (Box 21, Folder 1410)
      - Contract, 1978 May 23 (Box 21, Folder 1411)
      - Financial statement, 1980 Dec 15 (Box 21, Folder 1412)
      - Review, printed version, photocopy, undated (Box 21, Folder 1413)
  - Moody, A.D.
    - "Artful Voices: Eliot's Dramatic Verse"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1414)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1415)
    - "Cantos I-III: Craft and Vision"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1416)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1417)
  - Morgan, Anne
    - "Parc Monsourris: An Afternoon in Winter," typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1418)
  - Morwood, James
    - [Review] "Jumpers Revisited"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1419)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1420)
  - Moss, Howard
    - "Bay Days," printed version, undated (Box 21, Folder 1421)
  - Motion, Andrew
    - "Homecoming"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1422)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 1423)
      - Galley, undated (Box 21, Folder 1424)
  - Movie, Geoffrey
    - "Asopo"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1425)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1426)
  - Mrosovsky, Kitty
    - [Review] "Mallarmé: The Poems" and "Cross Channel" by Peter Dale"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1427)
      - Galley, undated (Box 21, Folder 1428)
    - "To cut a long story short," typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1429)
    - "Turning Point"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1430)
      - Galley, with author's corrections With: ANS from Kitty Mrosovsky to William Cookson, n.y. Feb 22 (Box 21, Folder 1431)
  - Mu, Tan (Mu Dan)
    - "The Flag," translated by Hu Shiguang, printed version, undated (Box 21, Folder 1432)
  - Mu, Yin
    - "Abandoned Women," typescript, original and translated by John Cayley, undated (Box 21, Folder 1433)
    - "A Case," typescript, original and translated by John Cayley, undated (Box 21, Folder 1434)